<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>humor on The Aiglet</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/tags/humor/</link><description>Recent content in humor on The Aiglet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:35:36 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theaiglet.top/tags/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida Bans Fluoride, Replaces with Corn Syrup in Bold Move for Sweeter, More Patriotic Teeth</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/florida-bans-flouride-corn-syrup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:35:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/florida-bans-flouride-corn-syrup/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, FL — In a groundbreaking decision that has dentists shaking their heads and soda companies popping champagne, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis signed into law today a bill that bans the &amp;ldquo;communist chemical&amp;rdquo; fluoride from the state&amp;rsquo;s water supply, replacing it with good old-fashioned high fructose corn syrup.
&amp;ldquo;Floridians have had enough of this liberal plot to control our precious bodily fluids,&amp;rdquo; declared Governor DeSantis at a press conference held at a Tampa-area Cinnabon.</description></item><item><title>Executive Order Allows Smoking on Planes, Citing "Freedom to Fume"</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/executive-order-smoking-planes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:55:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/executive-order-smoking-planes/</guid><description>WASHINGTON, D.C. — In a move that has left public health officials, airline executives, and non-smoking passengers gasping for air, President Chester B. Fogarty signed an executive order Tuesday officially allowing smoking on all domestic and international flights departing from U.S. soil.
Dubbed the &amp;ldquo;Freedom to Fume Act,&amp;rdquo; the order was announced aboard Air Force One, where the President lit a celebratory cigar and declared, &amp;ldquo;America was built on liberty, and nothing says liberty like lighting up at 30,000 feet.</description></item></channel></rss>