<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology on The Aiglet</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/tags/technology/</link><description>Recent content in Technology on The Aiglet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:45:24 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theaiglet.top/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Silicon Valley CEOs Turn to Private Jets for High-Altitude Smuggling Operations</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/silicon-valley-ceos-smuggling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:45:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/silicon-valley-ceos-smuggling/</guid><description>In a shocking turn of events, the world&amp;rsquo;s most powerful tech executives have found a new use for their private jets - smuggling high-value goods to avoid international tariffs. According to sources close to the situation, Silicon Valley&amp;rsquo;s elite are now using their luxury aircraft for more than just quick trips to their private islands.
&amp;ldquo;We realized we could save millions by flying our own goods across borders,&amp;rdquo; said Elon Musk, who was recently spotted landing his Gulfstream G650ER at a remote airstrip in the Cayman Islands.</description></item><item><title>Tech Titans Declare War on Manners: "Please" and "Thank You" Costing Us Billions</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/tech-titans-war-on-manners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:17:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/tech-titans-war-on-manners/</guid><description>In a groundbreaking press conference that left etiquette experts aghast, leading Silicon Valley CEOs announced a bold new initiative: the complete elimination of workplace pleasantries, which they claim are &amp;ldquo;crushing productivity&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;bleeding profits.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Every &amp;lsquo;please&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;thank you&amp;rsquo; is a microaggression against our bottom line,&amp;rdquo; declared Xander Blip, CEO of tech giant Nimbus AI, while aggressively mashing his keyboard for emphasis. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve crunched the numbers, and it turns out that basic human decency is costing the tech sector approximately $4.</description></item></channel></rss>