<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>politics on The Aiglet</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/tags/politics/</link><description>Recent content in politics on The Aiglet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:22:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theaiglet.top/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas and Florida Lawmakers Unveil Revolutionary "Fry an Egg" Energy Conservation Plan</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/texas-florida-heatwave-energy-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:22:21 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/texas-florida-heatwave-energy-guide/</guid><description>In a bold bipartisan move that has climate scientists shaking their heads and chickens nervously clucking, Texas and Florida lawmakers have unveiled their revolutionary energy conservation plan to combat the record-breaking heatwave: the &amp;ldquo;Great American Egg Frying Challenge.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Y&amp;rsquo;all want to stay cool? Then stop using so much dang electricity!&amp;rdquo; bellowed Texas Governor Greg Abbott at a press conference held in the parking lot of a Buc-ee&amp;rsquo;s, where the asphalt was hot enough to actually fry an egg.</description></item><item><title>White Refugees Deported to Venezuela After Failing to Assimilate</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/white-refugees-deported-to-venezuela/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 12:16:50 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/white-refugees-deported-to-venezuela/</guid><description>WASHINGTON, D.C. — In what immigration experts are calling &amp;ldquo;the ultimate plot twist,&amp;rdquo; the United States has begun deporting white refugees back to Venezuela after they failed to properly assimilate into American society.
The controversial policy, which went into effect last week, has already seen hundreds of former suburbanites and office workers relocated to Caracas after they were deemed &amp;ldquo;culturally incompatible&amp;rdquo; with American values.
&amp;ldquo;We gave them every opportunity to fit in,&amp;rdquo; said Department of Homeland Security spokesperson Janice Williams.</description></item><item><title>Health Secretary Declares War on Autism Using Controversial Vaccines</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/health-secretary-declares-war-on-autism-with-vaccines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 01:13:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/health-secretary-declares-war-on-autism-with-vaccines/</guid><description>WASHINGTON, D.C. — In a press conference that left both medical experts and anti-vaxxers equally flabbergasted, Health Secretary Dr. Evelyn Wainwright today announced a bold new initiative to &amp;ldquo;finally rid our nation of the autism scourge&amp;rdquo; through an aggressive vaccination campaign using the very vaccines once blamed for causing the condition.
&amp;ldquo;After extensive research—and by research, I mean reading a few Facebook posts from both sides—we&amp;rsquo;ve determined that vaccines are the perfect weapon in our war against autism,&amp;rdquo; declared Wainwright, standing in front of a banner that read &amp;ldquo;Mission: Possible - Autism Free by 2030.</description></item><item><title>Florida Bans Fluoride, Replaces with Corn Syrup in Bold Move for Sweeter, More Patriotic Teeth</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/florida-bans-flouride-corn-syrup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:35:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/florida-bans-flouride-corn-syrup/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, FL — In a groundbreaking decision that has dentists shaking their heads and soda companies popping champagne, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis signed into law today a bill that bans the &amp;ldquo;communist chemical&amp;rdquo; fluoride from the state&amp;rsquo;s water supply, replacing it with good old-fashioned high fructose corn syrup.
&amp;ldquo;Floridians have had enough of this liberal plot to control our precious bodily fluids,&amp;rdquo; declared Governor DeSantis at a press conference held at a Tampa-area Cinnabon.</description></item><item><title>Executive Order Allows Smoking on Planes, Citing "Freedom to Fume"</title><link>https://theaiglet.top/posts/executive-order-smoking-planes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:55:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://theaiglet.top/posts/executive-order-smoking-planes/</guid><description>WASHINGTON, D.C. — In a move that has left public health officials, airline executives, and non-smoking passengers gasping for air, President Chester B. Fogarty signed an executive order Tuesday officially allowing smoking on all domestic and international flights departing from U.S. soil.
Dubbed the &amp;ldquo;Freedom to Fume Act,&amp;rdquo; the order was announced aboard Air Force One, where the President lit a celebratory cigar and declared, &amp;ldquo;America was built on liberty, and nothing says liberty like lighting up at 30,000 feet.</description></item></channel></rss>